In Camera Filming
Filming in progress
Hello everyone! We are Potential Stary!
We are going to have a talk show with video creators Mr. Tsuruoka and Mr. Murakata!
Please give us your best regards!
Ladies and gentlemen, today is the opening stage for the first day of Nonaka Tatae on November 3!
I'm so happy to be here!
Now, what shall we talk about?
Tsuri-oka-san, I know you fish on a regular basis,
We have never fished.
Maybe only with fishing rafts or something.
That's right.
But I'm sure you know what kind of fish you can catch,
I'm sure she knows what kind of fish we can catch and many other things,
I am sure you know a lot of things about what kind of fish you can catch and so on, so when we eat and fish in the future
I would like to ask them what I want to know and get a lot of information.
So, I'll be looking in there, out there, and in there.
Hi please!
Please take care of us!
Thank you very much!
Nice to meet you!
I'm Megu!
We're in the shade,
You're really shining!
We're a little bit in the shadows.
We live in Fukuoka, but we don't have many chances to visit Saga.
We don't have many chances to visit Saga, so it would be nice if we could get to know each other's good points.
It would be nice if we could get to know each other's good points.
Thank you very much.
Good morning.
Welcome to Murakata. I look forward to working with you.
It's hot today, isn't it?
I went fishing yesterday, but because of the sudden heat, I couldn't catch any fish.
I didn't go, but Hataku went.
It was bad.
We fished all day. Do it for a day.
Good morning and thank you for your time.
Best regards.
Now I would like to greet you again.
Good morning. We are Bartenhardstein!
Pleased to meet you.
Am I demanding now?
Yes, I knew I was in the right track.
Right now?
Wait a minute, middle-aged college?
What's the name of that place?
Fishing is good, sir.
I look forward to working with you.
So, November 3rd, the Chest and Shoulders Festival has started.
Thank you very much.
We, the Batten Show Women's Squad, are the tourism ambassadors of Chest Shoulder City,
We have a YouTube channel and a Google channel, and we actually go to the fishing industry and fishing port in Chestnut Shoulder for interviews,
We also do drive-in live performances at the roadside station "Chest Shoulder" during the Corona Disaster,
I've been exposed to a lot of the charms of breast shoulder.
Today, I would like to talk about the charms of breast shoulder.
I think I don't need to explain anymore,
Tsuri-oka-san is a YouTube channel with over 1.7 million subscribers,
Tsurioka-san has over 1.7 million registered users on his YouTube channel, Tsurioka, right? He is one of the leading video creators in Saga and runs a YouTube channel with over 1.7 million registered users.
I would like to discuss the charms of Saga and the charms of breast shoulders with him.
Please give him my best regards.
Always to meet.
Uncle, I know I'm an uncle, but it's about time my back is in some kind of bad shape.
By the way, did you know we've met?
Yes, we have.
Oh, you know? Really? Really?
That's when we met.
You mean when you met her, or maybe you were filming her?
Yes. We met at Yutoku Inari Shrine in Saga,
Wow!
Music video.
You met at Yutoku Inari?
They were shooting a promotional video or something,
We were shooting a promotional video or something, and we were driving around, We were driving around in our car,
We happened to go to Yutoku Inari Shrine and saw them filming a music video,
I was watching them and thinking, "Wow, they have the guts of a wild horse.
They were filming a song called "Yoimiya" at Yutoku Inari Shrine in Saga Prefecture,
Also,
Underwater Trigger
When the salt recedes
When the salt recedes, you can pass through a torii gate.
I was filming there...
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
He just happened to show up there.
He was a beast!
And I think the bike was really noisy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think we had at least an emotional reunion.
That's true.
I didn't think you'd noticed.
It's finished, and it's a music video.
By the way, have you seen it?
Oh, I did!
You've seen it many times.
But I really did.
Thank you very much.
I was wondering if I was on it.
Well, take your time.
Hey, you should join us sometime.
I'd love to!
For the music video?
With you guys?
In the back.
We're the Batten Show Girls!
Saga Prefecture is one of them.
We filmed music videos in various places in Kyushu.
This was one of them.
And for the song "Sagashimana"...
Saga's Balloon Festa.
I'm just writing this now I'm writing this just now.
I shouldn't be telling you now.
Since most of you went to the Murakata Festival.
That's right.
I have a song about it and so on.
But if you ask me if I know a lot about Saga Prefecture
I don't.
I don't know much about it yet.
But it can't be helped.
It's at the bottom of the ranking of attractiveness.
We're at the bottom of the list.
It's only going to go up from here.
It's going up, isn't it?
That's how we got a head start, wasn't it?
After sinking quite a bit...
I'm going to be in fourth place.
I might be living in the sun.
By the way, are you here today?
Are you from Murakata?
Murakata.
What's the attraction of Saga Prefecture?
I'd like to hear.
Um...
Hata-kun, please.
What's that?
There's too much to choose from.
There's so much nature.
That's right.
I wonder if any of you have been to Saga.
Have you?
Yes, I have.
It's lovely.
What kind of places do you go?
Yobuko
When I get my driver's license, I tend to go to places that call me.
When I get my driver's license...
There's a difference. There's a difference.
It would be funny if I knew someone who knew someone who knew someone who knew someone who knew someone who knew someone who knew someone who knew someone who knew someone
When you get your driver's license...
That's exactly what Ai did.
I got my license for the first time.
Right?
I went to another artlet mall.
But there's something good about being a hometown.
Everyone feels at home back home.
I don't know...
The reason why I'm doing YouTube in Saga...
I just don't want to leave my hometown.
That's the charm of course.
The squid in Yobuko is delicious.
Marfesta and all that, but
But basically, our hometown is where we feel at home.
or a place where we feel at home.
I think it's just the right amount of countryside.
I think it gives us a sense of independence.
If we were actually going to be idols
I know that if we were to become idols, it would be more advantageous to stay in Tokyo.
But I don't want to leave Fukuoka.
I'm not coming to Tokyo!
I want to support you!
I want to support you! Go for it!
I'll become a fan!
What was that? I'll be a member!
I'm so happy!
By the way, we also have a great connection to the breast shape.
We come here at least once a week, maybe more like once a month.
We come here about once a month.
Fishing
They did a VTR of some kind for us.
Thank you very much!
We'll take a boat from there.
We'll take a boat from there and go near Ichigeki.
When we caught tuna, we went out from there.
I caught it! I caught it!
I got to say millions of views.
I caught a tuna that weighed, what, 80 kilos?
That's where I caught the tuna.
In the video, he said it weighed 100 kilograms.
But actually it weighed about 80 kilos.
But it's important, isn't it!
You're doing a great job! I'm rooting for you!
But is it really easier to catch fish
Does it make it easier to catch fish?
There's a place called the "sea junction tower"...
But that's where you fish from a chair.
The best sea out there by boat is...
It's a long way north of the thorax.
Between the pond and Tsushima?
Before the pond?
There's a rapids called Nanari before the pond.
I don't know how to say it.
It's all ocean.
But there's a good tide, the Kuroshio.
It flows to the Sea of Japan.
And there are a lot of bumps in it.
where there are a lot of bumps in the water, that's where you can fish.
There's a great fishing spot called Shichisato.
It's not too much to say it's the best in Japan.
It's probably the best in Japan.
By the way, has anyone ever fished there?
No one!
No? !
But you're the tourism ambassador of Thorax!
Then go out on a boat.
Can we go out on the boat?
Or we could do it as a regular show.
I think that's one of the great things about Kyushu.
You can catch a lot of fresh fish.
So when you say you've caught fish...
We'd like to say we've caught fish, too.
But we haven't had a chance to do so. I haven't had a chance to do it yet.
But there was a script that said
I found a script that called for collaboration.
So it's after this.
I'm sorry I haven't told you yet.
I'm still pretending it didn't happen.
It's just a selfish image of fishing.
Like putting a bug on a fish.
Non, non, non!
That's almost a thing of the past.
Is that so?
There are so many kinds of fishing nowadays.
There are only a few that use bait.
I don't use bait... much.
Without bait?
You won't catch anything.
You're so stupid.
That's not what I meant.
It's called a lure.
Let's do it.
I wanna fish.
Are there any precautions?
Like what to wear?
Sure.
I think I'll just wear this.
Is everything okay?
It's okay. I didn't wash it.
You wouldn't even know if there was a little blood on it.
No, it's fine.
It's easy to move around.
Basically, there are no precautions.
It's easy to get in.
The image of a life jacket...
with a life jacket and pants like these.
I know there are a lot of people
We want you to feel lightweight
We're not going to wear heavy equipment.It's not like we're going to equip ourselves with a lot of guts.
It's not like it's illegal.
So just dress as you normally would.
I'm just asking people to dress casually
I'm just trying to catch fish.
You don't have to touch the insects or anything like that.
You don't have to touch them.
and you don't have to touch anything.
I really want to go.
The other day, I collaborated with a woman
I did it with a woman from Jan-Pro, and she had a lot of fun.
She had a lot of fun.
Even if they have a bad image of me...
They thought I had such a good time.
I like that.
It's becoming more and more common now, isn't it?
Even women like it.
Yes, if it's meaningful, it's increasing.
It's increasing.
We are, too.
Debut?
I can't swim, but I'll be fine.
Why are we falling?
You'll get your fishing debut.
Then we'll make our idol debut the next time.
We'll do it together, dressed like that.
I'll do it.
You're gonna let me live?
We're all middle-aged and glowing.
Let's have some fun and dance together.
Sure.
It's really easy to dance.
It's so easy.
You'll be out of breath for the rest of your life.
You'll be out of breath for the rest of your life, if you don't show me that for a second.
Like the chorus.
Let's do the chorus.
I think you're really mimicking me. I really think you're imitating yourself.
You can do it right now.
Here we go.
First, where the eyes can be found
Jump on the voice.
You never look for it.
There's no limit to what you can do.
Let's just get on with it and go somewhere else.
Let's go look for him.
You sure you're up for this?
I can't. I can't. I can't.
It's too cute.
It's not a dance for a middle-aged man.
I was just admiring her.
And they were looking at me, so I was super embarrassed.
I thought, "Can I dance?
I'll give it my best shot.
At this point, my knees were killing me.
It was hard to move this way.
It's true that this song is pretty intense.
It seemed easy at first
but I couldn't do it from the middle of the song.
I can see why you're a fan.
It makes you want to cheer for them.
But I'm also getting interested in fishing.
Someday, I promise.
I'm getting interested in dancing, too.
I'll definitely dance.
Let's do it together
I'm looking forward to working with you.
If there is a real fishing collaboration in the future
I promise
Please do!
Murakata, Saka...
I'm looking forward to fishing with you!
So, thank you all for coming to see the show!
This stage was presented by
Batten Girls' Troupe and With Batten Girl Squad
Tsuri-Oka Tesho.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for watching.
If it's okay, I'd like to do it.
I like it.
It's so nice.
Everyone will support you.
Thank you very much.
We're the ones who are nervous.
But I'd rather do it on my chest and shoulders.
If it's big enough.
I'm always ready to fish.
All right!
Let's make Kyushu a great place to live together.
I'm looking forward to it.
Thank you very much.
I wish I could forget.
Mmm!
Yum!